<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="answer">
        <item>A bitcoin is a peer-to-peer paperless digital currency that came into existence in 2009. It is a decentralized form of currency that has not central regulator. It is controlled by the users. What this means is that no one, not even the government, can block your bitcoin transactions. You can transfer or receive bitcoins through your mobile phone without any bulky paperwork.</item>
        <item>The idea of having a cashless and decentralized money transfer system was conceptualized by an anonymous figure called Satoshi Nakamoto. In a white paper published in May 2008, Satoshi outlined in detail how the digital currency would work.</item>
        <item>One special thing about this digital currency is the fact that one can receive or send bitcoins without having to go through a third party. Transacting in other currencies requires third parties such as banks or financial intermediaries.</item>
        <item>Most cryptocurrencies are decentralized. This means that no single entity or groups control them. The advantage of decentralization is that the currency can be spent anywhere in the world provided that the recipient acknowledges bitcoins as a form of payment.</item>
        <item>Bitcoins are similar to paper money in that they can be spent or used to settle debt. For some people, bitcoins are an investment because of their ever increasing value. For others, they are used for transferring money internationally. Bitcoins are stored in electronic digital wallets. These digital wallets can either be desktop, mobile, hardware or even online based.</item>
        <item>The exact number of bitcoin users is hard to determine. This is because there are no official central records of the users. However, this number can be estimated based on the number of digital currency wallets. As of September 2017, there were about 20 million active bitcoin wallet users. Generally, there is a steady increase in the number of people transacting in bitcoins.</item>
        <item>There are three ways of getting bitcoins. The first one is through mining. Initially, this was a very profitable venture. It is no longer, however, cost effective for individuals. In this method, one buys specialized mining equipment, rents spaces for them digitally and pays the associated costs for them. The associated costs include cooling, electricity and rental costs.</item>
        <item>Every bitcoin wallet has its own unique address. This address represents a destination. The address is usually alphanumeric having between twenty seven and thirty four characters in length. Most wallets are user friendly and have interfaces that are easy to navigate. If you want to send bitcoins, you must first ensure that your wallet balance is positive.</item>
        <item>Bitcoin transactions are cheap. Normal currency transactions are expensive, especially where large amounts of money are involved. Another advantage of transacting in bitcoins is that it is tax free. Since it is not controlled by the government, no duties or taxes are payable by either party.</item>
        <item>Bitcoin transactions are cheap. Normal currency transactions are expensive, especially where large amounts of money are involved. Another advantage of transacting in bitcoins is that it is tax free. Since it is not controlled by the government, no duties or taxes are payable by either party.</item>
        <item>is where I am buying and selling most of my Steem and Steem Dollars into Bitcoin because the transactions complete in about half an hour total from sending SBD to Bittrex to having USD in my Coinbase wallet. For buying into Steem, the reverse is true where I can have my USD changed into Steem in my wallet at the best rate in about thirty minutes. Poloniex is what I used previously but many users have been unable to make withdrawals leaving me to suspect a crash is coming.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>